<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../schema/dreams.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<dr:dreams xmlns:dr="dream" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
  <dr:dream>
    <dr:date>2020-06-07</dr:date>
    <dr:description>
      Back in Moscow, the school. What a hellhole. Shook hands with the head teacher, the witch. Mass gathering of students.
      Covid scares. I want to get out of here. 
      Got a message from my Russian friend. I probably didn't answer.
    </dr:description>
  </dr:dream>
  <dr:dream>
    <dr:date>2020-06-09</dr:date>
    <dr:description>
     Family gathering. Many people, crowded even. Running around. I lost my shoe. I lost my pants. I feel ashamed. I lost a card game. My little sister won everything.
     I See my grandmother, in her old house, celebrating New Year in the summer.
    </dr:description>
  </dr:dream>
  <dr:dream>
    <dr:date>2020-06-11</dr:date>
    <dr:description>
      M. invites me to her wedding. I am together with my brothers and mom in some strange house. L. wants me to go shopping for him. I get angry,
      I'm working from home. Discussed with C. that my work can't be done that easily.
    </dr:description>
  </dr:dream>  
  <dr:dream>
    <dr:date>2020-06-12</dr:date>
    <dr:description>
      Played a video game with my brothers. I had invited them to my lonely apartment near the sea. I did my best not to make them bored. Did we lose H.?
      L. came back to work. I'm happy.
    </dr:description>
  </dr:dream>
  <dr:dream>
    <dr:date>2020-06-14</dr:date>
    <dr:description>Back in Russia. This time I'm a student, it seems. Further details elude me.</dr:description>
  </dr:dream>
  <dr:dream>
    <dr:date>2020-06-15</dr:date>
    <dr:description>On a bike,in the dark. It's some kind of game. I see dead people next to the road. 
      I'm in L. I meet with K., an old classmate. We're in love. We have no place to meet. I then go to dark-haired T., who is sitting at a table outside. 
      She's accompanied by her boyfriend. Too bad. She is cold and they decide to walk away. I go back home. My bike breaks. My phone screen is shattered. I've accidentally changed the pin number. 
      I enter an underground bar with my bike. The back door says bikes are not allowed. Luckily, the bartender doesn't seem to care. </dr:description>
  </dr:dream>
</dr:dreams>

