<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../schema/dreams.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<dreams xmlns="dream">
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-07</date>
    <description> Back in Moscow, the school. What a hellhole. Shook hands with the head teacher, the witch. Mass gathering of students. Covid scares. I want to get out of here. Got a message from my
      Russian friend. I probably didn't answer. </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-09</date>
    <description> Family gathering. Many people, crowded even. Running around. I lost my shoe. I lost my pants. I feel ashamed. I lost a card game. My little sister won everything. I See my
      grandmother, in her old house, celebrating New Year in the summer. </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-11</date>
    <description> M. invites me to her wedding. I am together with my brothers and mom in some strange house. L. wants me to go shopping for him. I get angry, I'm working from home. Discussed with C.
      that my work can't be done that easily. </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-12</date>
    <description> Played a video game with my brothers. I had invited them to my lonely apartment near the sea. I did my best not to make them bored. Did we lose H.? L. came back to work. I'm happy.
    </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-14</date>
    <description>Back in Russia. This time I'm a student, it seems. Further details elude me.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-15</date>
    <description>On a bike,in the dark. It's some kind of game. I see dead people next to the road. I'm in L. I meet with K., an old classmate. We're in love. We have no place to meet. I then go to
      dark-haired T., who is sitting at a table outside. She's accompanied by her boyfriend. Too bad. She is cold and they decide to walk away. I go back home. My bike breaks. My phone screen is
      shattered. I've accidentally changed the pin number. I enter an underground bar with my bike. The back door says bikes are not allowed. Luckily, the bartender doesn't seem to care.
    </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-18</date>
    <description>I turned into a cannibal. I am eating human flesh. It disgusts me. It tastes horrible. I throw it away and hope I will avoid any weird diseases.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-26</date>
    <description>I am at work. We are running towards a bus stop. A lot of us were tired afterwards. I talk to H. and K. I hope the latter can explain why nothing is working. I am wearing light
      colored pants.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-27</date>
    <description>A beautiful, large hotel by the seaside. Somebody is getting married. I feel confused and out of place. I want to go for a walk on the beach. Quickly, before the sun goes down. My family is there. So are my colleagues.
      They are looking for a room. </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-07-01</date>
    <description>Playing a video game with L. and S. I find it hard and don't know what to do. I get frustrated.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-07-02</date>
    <description>I am in a game. I am on a wagon, fighting with somebody. We keep stabbing each other. I am mashing buttons.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-07-05</date>
    <description>At school. Getting in a classroom with colleagues. S. forces me to buy gifts for my brothers. I am lying on the floor. There is some kind of party I don't care about. I am trading my games with K.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-07-09</date>
    <description>Living in a big house. T. lives thereas well. I need to make sure I clean up after myself. I don't want T. to leave.</description>
  </dream>
</dreams>
