<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../schema/dreams.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<dreams xmlns="dream">
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-07</date>
    <description> Back in Moscow, the school. What a hellhole. Shook hands with the head teacher, the witch. Mass gathering of students. Covid scares. I want to get out of here. Got a message from my
      Russian friend. I probably didn't answer. </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-09</date>
    <description> Family gathering. Many people, crowded even. Running around. I lost my shoe. I lost my pants. I feel ashamed. I lost a card game. My little sister won everything. I See my
      grandmother, in her old house, celebrating New Year in the summer. </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-11</date>
    <description> M. invites me to her wedding. I am together with my brothers and mom in some strange house. L. wants me to go shopping for him. I get angry, I'm working from home. Discussed with C.
      that my work can't be done that easily. </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-12</date>
    <description> Played a video game with my brothers. I had invited them to my lonely apartment near the sea. I did my best not to make them bored. Did we lose H.? L. came back to work. I'm happy.
    </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-14</date>
    <description>Back in Russia. This time I'm a student, it seems. Further details elude me.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-15</date>
    <description>On a bike,in the dark. It's some kind of game. I see dead people next to the road. I'm in L. I meet with K., an old classmate. We're in love. We have no place to meet. I then go to
      dark-haired T., who is sitting at a table outside. She's accompanied by her boyfriend. Too bad. She is cold and they decide to walk away. I go back home. My bike breaks. My phone screen is
      shattered. I've accidentally changed the pin number. I enter an underground bar with my bike. The back door says bikes are not allowed. Luckily, the bartender doesn't seem to care.
    </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-18</date>
    <description>I turned into a cannibal. I am eating human flesh. It disgusts me. It tastes horrible. I throw it away and hope I will avoid any weird diseases.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-26</date>
    <description>I am at work. We are running towards a bus stop. A lot of us were tired afterwards. I talk to H. and K. I hope the latter can explain why nothing is working. I am wearing light
      colored pants.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-06-27</date>
    <description>A beautiful, large hotel by the seaside. Somebody is getting married. I feel confused and out of place. I want to go for a walk on the beach. Quickly, before the sun goes down. My
      family is there. So are my colleagues. They are looking for a room. </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-07-01</date>
    <description>Playing a video game with L. and S. I find it hard and don't know what to do. I get frustrated.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-07-02</date>
    <description>I am in a game. I am on a wagon, fighting with somebody. We keep stabbing each other. I am mashing buttons.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-07-05</date>
    <description>At school. Getting in a classroom with colleagues. S. forces me to buy gifts for my brothers. I am lying on the floor. There is some kind of party I don't care about. I am trading my
      games with K.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-07-11</date>
    <description>Running home from the football club. My endurance is endless. I run so fast. I never knew how much I like running. There was a festival going on where I was with my brothers...I am
      now far from home. I support those that didn't make it, as we go up the stairs. We switched rooms, but I forgot to take my glasses with me. They were broken. I hope the hotel staff managed to
      find them. </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-07-09</date>
    <description>Living in a big house. T. lives there as well. I need to make sure I clean up after myself. I don't want T. to leave.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-07-08</date>
    <description>I have been hosting parties. B. is preparing a steak. P. can't control himself. I'm in a book shop. I've forgotten my own books.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-07-14</date>
    <description>I am in a cave. Abroad, on a university assignment. We need to find our way out of it. We have books that should help us. They contain maps. I see other people solving the same puzzle. I get three hours to find the exit. I feel confident. It's my old professor W. who leads the class.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-07-16</date>
    <description>In Moscow. In a shop underground, near the metro entrance. I suddenly realize I'm not wearing my face mask and quickly put it on. Then it comes. A flood of people coming in, heading towards the subway.
    They are not wearing masks. This is not good. We need to go. I wonder if it's better to wait, but then I realize Moscow is always busy. Waiting at the entrance restaurant now. We reserved places, but apparently I didn't. They're looking at me. Can't you just add a chair? 
    </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-07-17</date>
    <description>With my father in a gym. The gym is pretty much empty. The equipment looks old and beat up. The subscription fee is high, but we're here on a trial. 
    People are coming in. I want to get on a treadmill, but they're all taken. I settle for some weird machine that goes up and down. There is also a swimming pool in the middle. Outside
      there is a movie theatre. I think we're going to watch one. Did I forget something in the gym?
    </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-08-04</date>
    <description>Primary school bully T. made an appearance. I think I beat him up.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-09-01</date>
    <description>Driving with that man D. DB. Friendly man. Scary man.</description>
  </dream> 
   <dream>
      <date>2020-09-22</date>
      <description>I broke my glasses. Again. They are beyond salvaging. I'm in trouble now. I'm scared. I should have bought a better pair. M. proposes weird things.</description>
   </dream>
  <dream>
      <date>2020-10-14</date>
      <description>Leaving work. Taking the train and bus to some place. I ask when they go back, because I have to go back to work later. In an hour or so. I'm in a store.
     I buy lots of stuff, but I don't have a cart. I wanted to steal one from the cleaning lady. There's not much time left. Back in my old house, with other people. We need to leave, but the others haven't
     come back yet. There they are. I'm the last to get up. There's not enough space for me to get in the car. I consider not going. I get in anyway.
    </description>
   </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-10-18</date>
    <description>I am sitting on a chair in an unknown house. My mom races down the chairs. I try to hide the two cookies on my desk, but I think she saw them.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-10-15</date>
    <description>I am in someone else's house. K. is here. I turn on the TV. A show is about to begin, but we watch basketball instead. An old game, it seems.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-10-15</date>
    <description>I'm going on vacation. Don't know where. It seems like a nice country. I come across other tourists. I start talking to them. They are nice people. I arrive at the hostel. All beds are occupied. S. is here. I don't know where I am.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-11-07</date>
    <description>I am once again in an unknown house. I think I live here, together with other people. I am alone. I go to the toilet. It hasn't been flushed. I flush it, but it doesn't help. Is it mine?
      I need to take care of this before the others  return. Somebody arrives. I don't know him. </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-11-11</date>
    <description>In Moscow, teaching. I need to review my students. One group has been OK. I don't really know them. </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-11-16</date>
    <description>Stopping at a sandwich shop. I see my dad and the family sitting there. I order egg salad. The woman looks a little confused. 
    It's not on the menu. I don't have a mask, she gives me one. There are more people now. I want to be careful. My family gets up. The youngest was ignoring me. My sandwich is ready. Time to leave. I don't return the mask. I see my mother's side of the family. The place is crowded now. My mom walks me to my bike. </description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-12-03</date>
    <description>At work. T. is sitting close to me. We don't talk. We ignore each other.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-12-04</date>
    <description>Back in university. Professor P. is teaching. I am carrying weird stuff. I'm sitting in the train. I pretend to call the police, because I think the man sitting next to me has bad intentions. I'm in a kayak. Sports day. I'm not wearing my glasses. I meet a girl working for a French broadcaster.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-12-05</date>
    <description>My family and I are driving on the K.S. R. runs a red light, we are stopped by the police. We are fined. I continue by foot to school. It's the last day of school and I don't want to miss it. In a restaurant now with a whole bunch of people. I don't feel at home. I have a plate of cat in front of me. Strange, I didn't order  that.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-12-12</date>
    <description>I'm at home. I go to the big kitchen. A big kitchen? It has a dishwasher, tables, pots and pans. Why don't I come here more often? Right, it is shared with the neighbors. Where are they? Suddenly, a large group of people enter. Young people. I start talking to one of them. I tell him it's a bad idea to gather in large groups. I tell him I will kill him if I lose somebody because of him.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2020-12-19</date>
    <description>We're at a party. I silently leave. I am wearing two sweaters and listening to music. I don't like popular music. I walk down the street. A young boy approaches me. I ask him if he has heard of social distancing. A whole chain of people approaches me. I manage to avoid them. Apparently it's a marriage rite. I arrive at the library. They are spraying fake snow. I sit down. There are a boy and a girl sitting next to me. They are speaking Russian.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2021-01-05</date>
    <description>Running..running...even my dad is running. From the swimming pool to our home. The second swimming pool was not as fun as the first one, which is why I left early. So much running is good for my weight. I prefer to go the shop myself, otherwise they might give me something unhealthy. But won't they find that odd? Some other people arrive. I let them in. I don't know them.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2021-01-06</date>
    <description>School. We are invited somewhere. Two young women are selling it to us. It seems I ask strange questions. The other students laugh at me.</description>
  </dream>
  <dream>
    <date>2021-01-18</date>
    <description>Schumacher lives!</description>
  </dream>     
</dreams>
